<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PisoPatrol</string>
    <string name="instructions_text">Home Instructions:\n\n
Overview:\n
The Home provides an overview of recent transactions, current savings, and saving status.\n\n
Recent Transactions:\n
At the top of the, recent transactions are displayed.\n
Each transaction includes details such as title, amount, type (expense or allowance), category (if applicable), duration, and notes.\n
Transactions are listed with the most recent ones appearing first.\n\n
Savings:\n
The current savings amount is displayed prominently on the screen.\n
It reflects the total amount saved up to the present moment.\n\n
Savings Status:\n
The saving status indicates the financial health based on the ratio of savings to expenses.\n
It categorizes the status as Poor, Very Poor, Excellent, Very Good, or Good.\n\n
Dropdown Menu:\n
Clicking on the dropdown menu (three dots icon) located at the top right corner allows users to access additional options.\n\n
Additional Options:\n
The dropdown menu provides options to reset data and view information about the application.\n\n
Add Transaction Instructions:\n
Overview:\n
The Add Transaction enables users to input new transactions into the application.\n\n
Transaction Details:\n
Users can input details such as title, amount, transaction type (expense or allowance), category (for expenses), duration (for allowances), and notes.\n\n
Transaction Type Selection:\n
Users can select whether the transaction is an expense or an allowance using radio buttons.\n
When the expense option is selected, users can choose a category for the expense transaction.\n
When the allowance option is selected, users can choose a duration for the allowance transaction.\n\n
Add Button:\n
Clicking the \'Add\' button adds the transaction to the application.\n
If the transaction is an expense, it deducts the amount from the current savings.\n
If the transaction is an allowance, it adds the amount to the current savings.\n\n
Transactions Instructions:\n
Overview:\n
The Transactions displays a list of transactions along with filtering options and transaction statistics.\n\n
Transaction List:\n
Transactions are listed in a RecyclerView.\n
Users can scroll through the list to view all transactions.\n\n
Filtering:\n
Users can filter transactions by selecting options from the dropdown spinner.\n
Filter options include \'All\', \'Expense\', and \'Allowance\'.\n\n
Transaction Statistics:\n
Below the transaction list, a PieChart visualizes transaction statistics.\n
It shows the distribution of expenses and allowances across different categories.\n
Users can see the percentage breakdown of each category.\n\n
PieChart Legend:\n
A legend is displayed below the PieChart, indicating the categories and their corresponding colors.</string>
</resources>
